(Raj:)-I'm not going to punch you.
-That's what my sister used to say.
-Look, do you wanna do this or not?
-I'm sorry. Proceed.
All right, ahem...
(Raj:)...imagine yourself in the one place
you feel most at home.
(Raj:)-Where is that?
-SimCity.
More specifically, the SimCity
I designed, Sheldonopolis.
(Raj:)Okay, you're in Sheldonopolis.
(Sheldon:)Where exactly? Sheldon Square?
(Sheldon:)Sheldon Towers? Sheldon Stadium,
home of the fighting Sheldons?
(Raj:)Whatever you like.
(Sheldon:)I thought this was supposed to be
guided meditation.
(Raj:)Fine, you're in Sheldon Square.
Really? This time of the year?
It's a bit nippy.
(Raj:)Then put on a sweater.
(Sheldon:)Suppose I could run downtown
and pick up something at Shel-Mart.
(Raj:)Yeah. Whatever.
Just go buy a sweater.
(Sheldon:)The nice thing about Shel-Mart is
I own it, so I get a 15 percent discount.